SPEAKER_02: Speaker 2 speaking segment 1
SPEAKER_00: Speaker 0 speaking segment 2
SPEAKER_01: Speaker 1 speaking segment 3
SPEAKER_00: Speaker 0 speaking segment 4
SPEAKER_01: Speaker 1 speaking segment 5
SPEAKER_00: Speaker 0 speaking segment 6
SPEAKER_02: Speaker 2 speaking segment 7
SPEAKER_00: Speaker 0 speaking segment 8
SPEAKER_02: Speaker 2 speaking segment 9
SPEAKER_00: Speaker 0 speaking segment 10
SPEAKER_02: Speaker 2 speaking segment 11
SPEAKER_00: Speaker 0 speaking segment 12
SPEAKER_02: Speaker 2 speaking segment 13
SPEAKER_00: Speaker 0 speaking segment 14
SPEAKER_02: Speaker 2 speaking segment 15
SPEAKER_01: Speaker 1 speaking segment 16
SPEAKER_00: Speaker 0 speaking segment 17
SPEAKER_01: Speaker 1 speaking segment 18
SPEAKER_00: Speaker 0 speaking segment 19
SPEAKER_01: Speaker 1 speaking segment 20
SPEAKER_00: Speaker 0 speaking segment 21
SPEAKER_02: Speaker 2 speaking segment 22
SPEAKER_00: Speaker 0 speaking segment 23
SPEAKER_02: Speaker 2 speaking segment 24
SPEAKER_00: Speaker 0 speaking segment 25
SPEAKER_02: Speaker 2 speaking segment 26
SPEAKER_01: Speaker 1 speaking segment 27
SPEAKER_00: Speaker 0 speaking segment 28
SPEAKER_02: Speaker 2 speaking segment 29
SPEAKER_00: Speaker 0 speaking segment 30
SPEAKER_02: Speaker 2 speaking segment 31
SPEAKER_00: Speaker 0 speaking segment 32
SPEAKER_01: Speaker 1 speaking segment 33
SPEAKER_00: Speaker 0 speaking segment 34
SPEAKER_02: Speaker 2 speaking segment 35
SPEAKER_00: Speaker 0 speaking segment 36
SPEAKER_02: Speaker 2 speaking segment 37
SPEAKER_00: Speaker 0 speaking segment 38
SPEAKER_02: Speaker 2 speaking segment 39
SPEAKER_00: Speaker 0 speaking segment 40
SPEAKER_01: Speaker 1 speaking segment 41
SPEAKER_00: Speaker 0 speaking segment 42
SPEAKER_02: Speaker 2 speaking segment 43
SPEAKER_00: Speaker 0 speaking segment 44
SPEAKER_02: Speaker 2 speaking segment 45
SPEAKER_00: Speaker 0 speaking segment 46
SPEAKER_02: Speaker 2 speaking segment 47
SPEAKER_00: Speaker 0 speaking segment 48
SPEAKER_02: Speaker 2 speaking segment 49
SPEAKER_00: Speaker 0 speaking segment 50
SPEAKER_02: Speaker 2 speaking segment 51
SPEAKER_00: Speaker 0 speaking segment 52
SPEAKER_01: Speaker 1 speaking segment 53
SPEAKER_00: Speaker 0 speaking segment 54
SPEAKER_02: Speaker 2 speaking segment 55
SPEAKER_00: Speaker 0 speaking segment 56
SPEAKER_02: Speaker 2 speaking segment 57
SPEAKER_00: Speaker 0 speaking segment 58
SPEAKER_02: Speaker 2 speaking segment 59
SPEAKER_00: Speaker 0 speaking segment 60
SPEAKER_02: Speaker 2 speaking segment 61
SPEAKER_00: Speaker 0 speaking segment 62
SPEAKER_02: Speaker 2 speaking segment 63
SPEAKER_00: Speaker 0 speaking segment 64
SPEAKER_02: Speaker 2 speaking segment 65
SPEAKER_00: Speaker 0 speaking segment 66
SPEAKER_02: Speaker 2 speaking segment 67
SPEAKER_00: Speaker 0 speaking segment 68
SPEAKER_02: Speaker 2 speaking segment 69
SPEAKER_00: Speaker 0 speaking segment 70
SPEAKER_01: Speaker 1 speaking segment 71
SPEAKER_00: Speaker 0 speaking segment 72
SPEAKER_01: Speaker 1 speaking segment 73
SPEAKER_00: Speaker 0 speaking segment 74
SPEAKER_02: Speaker 2 speaking segment 75
SPEAKER_00: Speaker 0 speaking segment 76
SPEAKER_02: Speaker 2 speaking segment 77
SPEAKER_00: Speaker 0 speaking segment 78
SPEAKER_02: Speaker 2 speaking segment 79
SPEAKER_00: Speaker 0 speaking segment 80
SPEAKER_01: Speaker 1 speaking segment 81
SPEAKER_00: Speaker 0 speaking segment 82
SPEAKER_01: Speaker 1 speaking segment 83
SPEAKER_00: Speaker 0 speaking segment 84
SPEAKER_02: Speaker 2 speaking segment 85
SPEAKER_00: Speaker 0 speaking segment 86
SPEAKER_01: Speaker 1 speaking segment 87
SPEAKER_00: Speaker 0 speaking segment 88
SPEAKER_02: Speaker 2 speaking segment 89